Kouki-kun!
Let's go.
Let's stay a bit longer.
It's time to sleep.
I'm not tired at all.
Let's go, Kouki-kun.
Let's go home.
Go on ahead.
I'll take you to a good place.
Good place?
Is it okay to take a detour?
Sure.
Man, you're heavy.
Don't put me down!
Do you have a fish tank at home?
No, but I have this.
That won't do.
Once you get home, fill a bucket with tap water
and put it in there.
Why?
Because tap water is rich in calcium.
Rin-chan.
Stay still.
Here you go.
You're going to get left behind!
Don't put me down!
Let's go.
Okay.
This is the place.
Oh, it's a river!
I'm coming too!
I didn't know there was such a place.
Is Rin-chan here for the first time as well?
Yes.
I suppose it's my first summer with Rin.
It's dark and I can't see a thing.
Daikichi, explain.
Come over here.
Let's go.
Wait up!
It's pretty late, but I still want to play.
You're not the only one.
This way, Kouki.
Good night!
See ya.
Good night.
Let's go.
You've grown taller.
「The Way Back Home」